<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Medical Image on Jiaming Zhang</title>
    <link>http://jmz3.github.io/tags/medical-image/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Medical Image on Jiaming Zhang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jmz3.github.io/tags/medical-image/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SAMME: Segment Any Medical Model Extended</title>
      <link>http://jmz3.github.io/posts/sam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://jmz3.github.io/posts/sam/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m excited to announce that our project SAMM has received many attentions from all over the world! Please reach out if you want to collaborate. SAMM allows users to directly leverage the powerful Segment Anything Model (SAM) to segment medical images (including CT, MR, Ultrasound, and more) in 3D Slicer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PoseHub: Surgical Tool Tracking with AR Headset</title>
      <link>http://jmz3.github.io/posts/ar-track/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://jmz3.github.io/posts/ar-track/</guid>
      <description>PoseHub: Surgical Tool Tracking with AR Headset Link to heading We are developing a surgical tool tracking system that can be used with augmented reality headsets. The system is designed to provide real-time feedback to the surgeon about the location of the surgical tool. The system has a scene-graph structure that allows for easy integration with different tracking devices and visualization tools. A synthetic dataset is generated in ROS to test the system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XREGI: Learning-based 2D/3D Fluoroscopic Image Registration</title>
      <link>http://jmz3.github.io/posts/xregi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://jmz3.github.io/posts/xregi/</guid>
      <description>Learning-based 2D/3D Fluoroscopic Image Registration Link to heading We developed and maintained an open-source python package xregi that is used to compute the projection matrix between 2D x-ray images and 3D CT scans. This process is also called as 2D/3D fluoroscopic image registration problem. The package is now available on Pypi. Install the pacakge through pip install xregi to try out!</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
